newagepregnancy.com 2017-07-22

# Privacy Policy | Pregnancy in Singapore

#### This is the Privacy Policy of **New Age Consulting Pte Ltd** and/or our related entities, affiliates and subsidiaries for our websites [New Age Parents](http://thenewageparents.com/) and [New Age Pregnancy](http://newagepregnancy.com/).

#### We are committed to protecting your privacy. We have developed this Privacy Policy to describe to you our practices regarding the information we collect from users of our services when you visit our websites, when you give us information or send us communications.

#### We have taken care to abide by the Singapore Personal Data Protection Act to collect, store and use your personal data fairly and lawfully and with due respect to the individual whose personal data is being processed.

#### **What information do we collect from you?**  
Depending on your usage of our websites and services, the information we typically collect may include your identification number, gender, date of birth, mailing address, email address, telephone and mobile numbers, country of residence, IP address, your preferences as well as any information about you that is associated with, or linked to, any other data that helps us to provide you with a more personal and relevant experience.

#### **How do we collect your information?**  
We may collect your personal information when you visit our websites, when you choose to use the various services we provide or when you provide information voluntarily. These include signing up for alerts or newsletters, contacting us with a question or requesting for assistance, participating in our forums, participating in contests or lucky draws and/or responding to surveys, questionnaires or offers.

#### **How will we use the information you give us?**  
Information provided by you may be used and disclosed by us and our affiliates, business partners for the following purposes:

#### (a) to provide you with the products and services you have requested and to communicate with you about those products and services;

#### (b) to respond to your requests and queries;

#### (c) to deliver the daily operation of the content, services and products provided to you;

#### (d) to verify and process your personal particulars and payments;

#### (e) to design services or products for customers’ use;

#### (f) to organise promotional events;

#### (g) to inform you (with your consent) about any products or services which may be of interest to you;

#### (h) to comply with legal requirements, the requests of law enforcement and regulatory officials, or orders of court;

#### (i) to invite you to share your opinions and comments; and

#### (j) to conduct surveys and/or market research.

#### In addition, please note that if you participate in contests or other promotional programs on our websites sponsored or organized by third parties or purchase goods and services offered by third parties or offer goods and services to third parties on our websites, your information may be disclosed to and used by such third parties.

#### **Do we share your information with other companies?**  
Unless otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not share your information with third parties for marketing purposes without your consent.

#### **Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please check back regularly for updated information on the handling of your personal data.
